Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his triumph, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
Metaplon
Why?
When I 대 Village
If anybody living with my eyes, I'm realized at a moment.
By feeling BIBLE
Guess what'sOMSIFE?
Thank you.
Yeah, that's all.
Hate to tell you, but I think they call that worrying.
Checking up on me, huh?
Thanks, Noelle.
I was worried about you, too.
I'm glad I'll create you made it back.
Well, you obviously needed the rest.
You know, conquering a dungeon and getting a major wound in the gut will really take it out of a guy.
I still think a whole week is a little excessive.
Enough of this boring chit-chat.
Think of my goddess Marie.
Would she enjoy such dull conversation?
Not one bit.
I need something interesting to tell her.
Like a story.
I only have 3,210 left.
And that's not enough to tide her over for a while?
How many stories does one girl need?
So, how are you?
That stomach wound all healed up now?
Are you ready to take me on?
Can we fight?
I don't think it's completely healed yet.
Although, maybe I'm just really hungry.
Hey, everybody!
Hope you brought your apple spice because the sheep cook's breakfast is ready!
Oh, wow!
This is delicious!
Will you slow down?
That's disgusting.
I'm...
Honestly, you are such a pig.
Hey, now.
The kiddo needs his sustenance to recover.
Wine to wash it down?
Sure, because that'll help.
So good!
That's it!
Don't be shy!
Show him how it's done, I'll stop!
The sheep cooks love a guy who knows how to eat!
Gonna grab some chow, then it's back to bed.
Oh, hey, Captain Yummy!
Good morning!
Good morning, Captain Yummy, sir!
So, kid, looks like you finally woke up.
Didn't die after all.
Nope!
Still alive, sir!
Well, good job out there.
Even if you did get yourself wrecked again.
Thank you, sir!
Right.
Now then, Knight's Headquarters wants a report on the dungeon ASAP.
So if you can walk, you're going.
What?
A report?
Oh, at Knight's Headquarters?
I bet there are tons of tough guys there.
Wonder how many I can fight!
I know that look on your face, and it means trouble.
No way you're going.
Aw!
I'm sending you out on a battle mission instead with Magna Babysitter.
A battle mission?
We'll make a great team, right, Magna?
Uh, what's with you?
How can I be sure you're really luck?
You could be gray in disguise.
Sure.
Never mind!
Hey, sir!
You can send me.
I don't mind going.
Really?
Just think of all the delectively done
going to chase the noble robot to offer!
They'll take this the wrong way,
but why the heck would I send you?
All you do is sit around eating all day.
What?
Captain, sir.
I'm sorry, but I can't go.
I'm busy writing letters to Marie.
Okay.
It's not like anyone asked you to go anyway.
I'm a good one, huh?
Whoa!
This is awesome!
I mean, I knew it was big, but up close it's huge!
Keep it down, would you?
You're embarrassing both of us right now.
So cool!
Stop yelling!
We're alone again.
Just me and him.
Enormous.
Gigantic.
Are you still going on about that?
It's not all that special, you know.
Oh, it's them.
Why, if it isn't the members of the Golden Dawn!
Hello there!
Hey, we haven't seen you since the dungeon, Asta.
I assume you've come to make your report, too?
Is your wound all healed up?
Yeah!
My stomach still hurts a bit, but after lots of food and sleep, I bounce back.
Such a child.
Who's a child here?
You.
You're the same age as me, you know!
Hey, I really owe you one, Mimosa.
Thanks so much for patching me up!
What's wrong?
Why'd she run away?
She was probably shocked to see how much shorter your arm is than she imagined it would be.
So.
And what the hell's that supposed to mean, huh?!
Seriously!
Just give up.
What's wrong, Mimosa?
You alright?
I don't know what to do!
Please help me!
It's, um, Asta.
Whenever I see him, I get this weird feeling in my chest.
Since that day in the dungeon, he's all I can ever seem to think about.
It's awful!
I don't know what's gotten into me!
Is that the way I just ran from him?
Do you think he's going to hate me now?
What can you possibly see in him?
He's a low-born, little-brained, loud-mouthed runt!
I think those things are all just part of his charm, honestly.
So much life in such a compact package.
Could this be...
No, no, no!
Not that muscle-bound freak!
Please, hold on.
Why am I so worked up about this?
No.
Not a chance!
Me and him?
Never!
What's all the moaning about?
Hmm.
Maybe their heads are hurting?
Knight's headquarters ought to be just through here.
Guess there are some things even you don't know, huh, Four Eyes?
Even we Four Eyes can't know everything.
I guess somewhere along the line he accepted his new nickname.
Wow, look how much better he's treating Asta.
Anyway,
we don't often come to headquarters,
so it's easy to forget.
No!
Is that really...
I never dreamed you would greet us personally, sir.
He's flashy.
Who do you think this guy is?
You idiot!
This is none other than the current Wizard King,
Sir Julius Novachrono.
It's actually him.
The Wizard King!
I'm pleased you were able to obtain this.
This magic is very powerful.
It could easily be that dungeon's greatest relic.
You can really read it, sir?
A little of it, yes.
The greatest relic in there?
Go us!
Hmm, let's see here.
Such excitement!
So the rumors of the Wizard King being an unparalleled magic geek were true.
What do you say?
Will you cast this spell for me, pretty please?
I'd love to see it!
I'm sorry, sir.
I believe it somehow activated once while we were in the dungeon.
But I haven't been able to use it again.
Oh, I see.
Well, too bad.
Sylph, Spirit of Wind.
One of the four major elements.
So he's the one she's chosen for this era.
I'm glad that you found this.
All I can tell you now is that this spell will grow as you do.
I believe it will be a tremendous help to you someday.
Okay, make sure you take good care of her, sir.
Wizard King, sir!
Some weird writing showed up in my Grim War, too!
Please take a look!
Don't be impertinent!
Hmm, this looks like...
Like what?
Something I can't read.
Huh.
I've never seen writing like that anywhere.
And this comes out of it!
What do you think, sir?
Oh.
A second anti-magic sword.
That's excellent.
Mine's working just fine.
The power of anti-magic.
May I...
Do you think I could hold it?
Go for it!
Thank you so...
Whoa!
Man!
Are you okay, Wizard King?
I'm amazed you can swing this thing around.
My magic power!
It's being sucked away!
Now I understand.
Thanks for letting me take a look.
Here you go.
I think you'd better hold on to it.
You may be the only one who can.
It's too much for me to handle, but you can wield it because you have no magic power.
I don't understand.
How do you know that I don't have any magic?
And about what my sword can do?
Well, you know, that's an excellent question.
Anyway, well done.
You did a marvelous job out there.
Much appreciated.
I just...
Can I...
Can I maybe ask you something, sir?
Sure.
What is it?
I was just wondering...
How can I become the Wizard King?
I see.
So the two of you are looking to become the Wizard King, are you?
Not surprising, given that you are magic knights.
You two must realize how rude it is to ask a question like that so directly.
Now listen.
The Wizard King must be of noble heart and have the implicit trust of all of his people...
No, Klaus.
It's about results.
A noble heart alone cannot protect anyone.
And the trust of the people is earned, not granted.
You want to know what you need to do to gain the title of Wizard King?
Get results.
Prove that you're the strongest.
Do what it takes.
Devote yourself to getting results.
That's all there is.
Anyone who's not capable of that cannot hope to stand at the summit.
Exactly what I wanted to hear.
Not bad, William.
Yummy.
I like the look in your newbie's eyes.
Now I hope you're ready for something special,
because today we've gathered those knights with an exceptional number of stars
for the Distinguished Service Ceremony.
The dis... what now?
The Distinguished Service Ceremony.
We give awards and commendations to those who have performed extraordinarily well.
I would appreciate it if you would join us for it.
This Distinguished Service Ceremony sounds fancy.
I wonder what it's going to be like.
Why us?
I have a bad feeling about this.
I hadn't expected this turn of events.
Here we are.
The question is, can you achieve greater results than these knights have?
All right.
Let the Distinguished Service Ceremony begin.
The Clover Kingdom's Magic Knights are given ranks based upon the caliber of their performance.
With the Wizard King at the top, the ranks are divided into five, from first through fifth class.
Knights gain rank through exemplary performance.
They must obtain the required number of stars before the annual Distinguished Service Ceremony,
when the Wizard King will bestow new ranks accordingly.
With a total of seven stars, from the Crimson Lion King squad, Leopold Vermillion, step forward.
I hereby bestow upon you the rank of Intermediate Magic Knight, second class.
Like your brother, Captain of the Crimson Lion Kings, your use of flame magic can be a bit overwhelming.
You may want to consider toning it down a little.
There's no room for mercy when you're fighting against evil, sir.
Next, with a total of six stars, from the Blue Rose Knights, Sol Maron.
I grant you the rank of Intermediate Magic Knight, third class.
Your vitality, a match for any man's, is amazing, as is your unique earth magic.
But perhaps you have a bit too much freedom.
The only person who can tie me down is Charlotte.
I mean, my captain.
Now, with a total of six stars, hailing from the Silver Eagles, I call Solid Silva.
I grant you the rank of Intermediate Magic Knight, third class.
You exhibit great skill in controlling your magic,
but it would be better if you could work with those around you rather than showing off your own powers.
I'll keep that in mind going forward.
With a total of nine stars, from the Silver Eagles, is Nebra Silva.
I grant you the rank of Senior Magic Knight, fifth class.
The illusions that you create with your mist magic are truly incredible.
But you have a habit of using them to toy with your foe more than necessary.
It may backfire someday.
Thank you for the advice.
I'll take it to heart.
With a total of seven stars.
Hailing from the Golden Dawn, Hammond Cassius.
I hereby grant you the rank of Intermediate Magic Knight, second class.
Looking at you, one wouldn't think you'd wield glass magic.
I imagine that often confuses your enemies.
Yes, sir, it does.
Thank you.
Next, with a total of eight stars.
Also from the Golden Dawn, Shirin Tiam.
I grant you the rank of Intermediate Magic Knight, first class.
Behind your eloquent magic is a reticent mage who rarely speaks his own mind.
I encourage you to make your thoughts and opinions known more often.
Sir.
And now with a total of eleven stars.
From the Golden Dawn, Alecdora Sandler.
I grant you the rank of Senior Magic Knight, fourth class.
I commend you for both your flexible magic and your diligent demeanor.
However, you might consider relaxing occasionally.
Welcome words, sir. Thank you.
Your efforts have helped bring the Golden Dawn's total to 71 stars.
A commanding lead.
The rest of you will have to work hard not to be left behind.
Well, that concludes the formal bit.
We've also prepared a simple banquet to celebrate the occasion.
So please enjoy yourselves.
And you may not have noticed, but I invited some special guests.
I hope you'll mix and mingle with them as well.
Pardon, sir.
I'm sorry, but something's come up.
You'll have to excuse me.
Have an excellent time now.
Their contempt is almost palpable.
How are we supposed to enjoy this?
Just look at them.
Why would the Wizard King subject us to this kind of treatment?
The man himself couldn't even stick around to witness it.
What is this?
I've never had anything like this.
Though it doesn't seem to have affected him much.
As unashamed as ever.
I wouldn't say unashamed.
More uncivilized.
Uh, excuse me.
I was thinking.
If you don't mind, maybe I'd join you?
Oh, sure, Mimosa.
So you've been eyeing this meat too, huh?
Oh, yes.
It looks very delicious.
Filthy gluttonous commoner.
Why would the Wizard King invite such a vulgar guest?
I can't sense any magic power in him.
If he did clear that dungeon, I'm sure it was purely by luck.
What a positively atrocious eater.
It's much like having a rat in the throne room.
His presence here is unnatural.
Huh?
You guys really don't play your punches, huh?
Oh, well, nothing I'm not used to.
It doesn't even seem to bother him!
If I remember correctly, you've got a commoner in your squad, too.
Everyone thinks he's a big deal because of his four-leaf clover grimoire.
But he's a commoner through and through.
They might have pulled off the dungeon-crawling mission.
But I have no doubt I would have done a better job.
Well, Crimson Lion Cub, aren't you full of yourself?
His work may be subpar, but it's not as if we expect much of a commoner.
True, he's Golden Dawn.
But it is we nobles who embody the ideals of our squad and captain.
Now, with all due respect...
And what about you, Klaus?
Klaus, a man of your caliber ought to be ashamed to be seen in the company of those commoners.
As for you, Mimosa, I hear you were promptly wounded in the dungeon and removed yourself from the front lines.
Your ineptitude is making Royal House Vermillion a laughingstock.
I-I'm sorry, I didn't mean to.
No! She performed admirably!
Come, Alecdora.
We all know who the most inept person here is.
And it's not poor little Mimosa.
Right, Noel?
Why, Solid? Why would you do that?
Enter your own sister!
You can't even control your magic properly.
Could there be any greater disgrace than you?
You were as good as banished from House Silva for being an abject failure.
How dare you come waltzing back into the noble realm as if you belong?
Nabra, please stop this!
You let a single success go to your head, and now you've come here to sully the Silva name with your presence.
But... we were invited!
This is no place for a pathetic creature like you.
Now leave.
Wasn't killing our mother enough?
Gah!
You don't need to run away from people like this, Noelle.
But... I...
You were invited here by the Wizard King, so I figured you had to be pretty amazing.
But you're just like all the rest of them, aren't you?
Commoner. Rat. Disgrace. Failure.
Do you think I care if I fit in with you people?
No! Watch! Because I will!
That's enough out of you, little rat.
We will not be spoken to in such a manner by your kind.
Be quiet.
Not a chance!
How dare you!
Now you better listen up, because I wasn't done talking!
I'm gonna get results like no one has before!
I'll do whatever it takes to become the Wizard King!
And prove you wrong!
, but...
Amo!
Eight!
Nine!
Ten!
Three!
Five!
Nine!
rat!
Ten!
Zero!
One!
Eight!
Ten!
One!
消えそうな光でも 闇を照らす力が
繋がって 時の流れを変える
色褪せない場所に
終わらない夢を掴むため 進むべき道があるなら
Do you wanna drive? Do you wanna drive? このままどこを待ってても
僕の命が終わるまで どんな痛みも受け入れよう
We can drive now! We can drive now!
たとえ明日が見えなくても 声にならない
想いを抱いて 叫び続ける in my heart
プリテッド
クロークエスト
月曜 月曜 マジエス
僕が初めを聞いた
同 twenties、フレーズな Hmm
メ撃ちの体がある
Asta, you're being incredibly rude to your Magic Knight superiors.
Now hurry up and say you're sorry.
I'll apologize along with you.
Black Clover, page 21, Capital Riot.
My magic is learning to accept some brat calling me four-eyes.